<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Construction &#8211; Greams Studio</title>
	<atom:link href="https://https://gamikajayawardana.github.io/greamsstudio/tag/construction/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://https://gamikajayawardana.github.io/greamsstudio</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 10:05:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Recent Commercial Real Estate Transactions</title>
		<link>https://https://gamikajayawardana.github.io/greamsstudio/2022/03/12/drivers-deliver-much-more-than-products/</link>
					<comments>https://https://gamikajayawardana.github.io/greamsstudio/2022/03/12/drivers-deliver-much-more-than-products/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[greamsstudio]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 11:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Construction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[transport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://codexpeed.com/transland/tips-to-lowering-freight-shipping-costs-copy/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We have a proven record of best result of building and reputable company in the United States. Thousands of successful projects we are one of the most trusted construction companies. We have a proven record of best result of building and reputable company in the United States. Northern anchovy–bass yellowtail barracuda zander yellowfin grouper gurnard [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We have a proven record of best result of building and reputable company in the United States. Thousands of successful projects we are one of the most trusted construction companies. We have a proven record of best result of building and reputable company in the United States.</p>
<p>Northern anchovy–bass yellowtail barracuda zander yellowfin grouper gurnard skipjack tuna shark burrowing goby eulachon wobbegong. Nase combtail gourami amur pike flabby whalefish; darter, Blind goby tuna. Eagle ray soa pearl perch bent-tooth stargazer grunion spookfish yellowtail Quillfish slickhead mora. snake worm mackerel sockeye salmon banjo catfish toadfish sauger four-eyed fish.</p>
<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-517" src="https://https://gamikajayawardana.github.io/greamsstudio/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/p2.jpg" alt="" width="894" height="382" /></p>
<h3>An Airborne Crisis on Two Fronts</h3>
<p>This shortage is being seen in both the airline and the cargo industries. With such a small pool of applicants to choose from, these two sectors are battling to get the most qualified available candidates. Many pilots are increasingly being wooed to get behind the controls of passenger planes over cargo flights—frankly, it’s tough to compete with jobs perks like fixed schedules and free flights for your family across the world.</p>
<blockquote><p>Thousands of successful projects we are one of the most trusted construction companies</p></blockquote>
<p>This is no anecdotal pilot shortage, either—the same problems are found on a global scale, with Boeing estimating an incredible shortage of 790,000 or more pilots across the world over the next two decades. In the shorter term, the domestic industry can expect more than 8,000 unfilled vacancies per year by 2020, and five years later that number could be higher than 12,000 pilot-less flights in need of help. This spells trouble for your supply chain because even if you don’t personally rely on flight to get items delivered, chances are at least one of your key suppliers does.</p>
<ul class="checked-list mb-3">
<li>We track every dollar</li>
<li>We’re an open book</li>
<li>100% goes to the field</li>
<li>Received the highest grades</li>
</ul>
<h3>Investing in Freight Broker Training</h3>
<p>Just as we’ve found with the truck driver shortage, the impetus behind skilled labor leaving is many-fold. Demographics play a large role—a massive amount of pilots are expected to hang up their hats in the next few years as they reach the mandatory commercial pilot retirement age of 65. And there’s no large group of applicants sitting waiting to replace them.This is likely because it’s becoming considerably more difficult to obtain a pilot license than it was ten years ago. <strong>After a 2009 Colgan Air crash, the US Federal Aviation Administration raised the requirements for an ATP certificate from 250 hours to a whopping 1,500 hours of training.</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://gamikajayawardana.github.io/greamsstudio/2022/03/12/drivers-deliver-much-more-than-products/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
